<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
  <head>
    <meta charset="UTF-8" />
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1.0" />
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="work.css" />
    <title>Travel with 63050132</title>
  </head>
  <body>
    <div class="homep">
      <div class="img">
        <img
          src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1_xL0QzU35S8UG0whX-dpog260fFiKX1J/view?usp=drive_link"
          alt="plane"
        />
      </div>
      <div class="text">
        <h2>TRAVEL</h2>
      </div>
      <div class="t1">
        <h3>HOME</h3>
      </div>
      <div class="t2">
        <h3>ABOUT</h3>
      </div>
      <div class="t3">
        <h3>PRODUCT</h3>
      </div>
      <div class="t4">
        <h4>Contact</h4>
      </div>
      <div class="icon">
        <link
          rel="stylesheet"
          href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/4.7.0/css/font-awesome.min.css"
        />
        <a
          href="https://www.facebook.com/"
          target="_blank"
          class="fa fa-facebook"
        ></a>

        <a
          href="https://twitter.com/i/flow/login?redirect_after_login=%2Flogin%3Flang%3Dth"
          target="_blank"
          class="fa fa-twitter"
        ></a>
        <a
          href="https://www.instagram.com/"
          target="_blank"
          class="fa fa-instagram"
        ></a>
      </div>
      <div class="about">
        <img
          src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1ZAyVndLeS8r0EsWsUqRWTIaJ02F2R0an/view?usp=drive_link"
          alt="travel"
        />
        <div class="tourism">
          <p>
            When it comes to tourism, it is the act of traveling to explore new
            things and experience various adventures that can enrich knowledge,
            enjoyment, challenges, and create significant memories. Tourism
            comes in various forms, including domestic and international travel,
            conventional sightseeing, and adventurous journeys. It can be
            categorized into several types based on the nature and purpose of
            the trip.
          </p>
          <br />
          <button class="btn">Contact us</button>
        </div>
        <div class="aboutp">
          <div class="tag">
            <img
              src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1599930113854-d6d7fd521f10?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1yZWxhdGVkfDN8fHxlbnwwfHx8fHw%3D&auto=format&fit=crop&w=500&q=60"
              alt="passport"
            />
          </div>
          <br />

          <h2>ABOUT US</h2>
          <h4>
            Our tourism company is an organization or business that focuses on
            providing services in the field of tourism. We have the capability
            to design and offer various tour packages, hotel reservations,
            accommodations, as well as manage and promote different tours for
            our customers. Our company aims to assist and enhance the travel
            experience for our clients, ensuring it is both impressive and
            efficient, so that they can enjoy their journey and explore various
            destinations as they expect. <br />
            <br />
            In addition to that, our tourism company can provide advice on
            tourist destinations, amenities, and interesting activities at each
            location, enabling our customers to plan their travels according to
            their preferences and interests. We also offer services tailored to
            group tours, business travel, and conferences, providing a diverse
            range of options to meet our customers' specific travel needs and
            desires.
          </h4>
          <div class="img1">
            <img
              src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1537824598505-99ee03483384?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1yZWxhdGVkfDE1fHx8ZW58MHx8fHx8&auto=format&fit=crop&w=500&q=60"
              alt="sea"
            />
            <img
              src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1519160558534-579f5106e43f?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxzZWFyY2h8NzZ8fHRyYXZlbHxlbnwwfHwwfHx8MA%3D%3D&auto=format&fit=crop&w=500&q=60"
              alt="forest"
            />
            <img
              src="https://images.unsplash.com/photo-1540741283650-38a15bbde41f?ixlib=rb-4.0.3&ixid=M3wxMjA3fDB8MHxwaG90by1yZWxhdGVkfDJ8fHxlbnwwfHx8fHw%3D&auto=format&fit=crop&w=500&q=60"
              alt="lake"
            />
          </div>
        </div>
        <div class="product">
          <br /><br />
          <h2>PRODUCT</h2>
          <br />
          <div class="China">
            <a href="https://www.qualityexpress.co.th/tour/China?keyword=&country=China&Airline=All&Airport=All&page=1&view=list" target="_blank">
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1J5xvkNYq0V-YvPHDaMLD7pf4RDZ-6DU4/view?usp=drive_link"
                alt="China"
              />
            </a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Japan : Finding accommodation options in Japan can be an exciting
              and diverse experience, ranging from traditional Japanese inns
              (Ryokan), guesthouses, hostels, or even joining Japan tours in
              cities like Kyoto, Nara, Hokkaido, and more.
            </p>
          </div>
          <div class="singapoer">
            <a
              href="https://www.khobfahtravel.com/package-tour/package-singapore/?gclid=Cj0KCQjw_O2lBhCFARIsAB0E8B_1SDOME6KffPhqwMTQQ-_iPEacMo9PziA4txSR4gCBD9ZNbKYKjA8aAoQJEALw_wcB"
              target="_blank"
            >
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1euiPsJLVg8kP97ttbncoOd3hUCThb1Dm/view?usp=sharing"
                alt="singapoer"
              />
            </a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Singpoer : Accommodation in Singapore either a hotel or a
              first-class resort and accommodation that fits many budgets. There
              are also rooms close to major attractions. and tours in Singapore
              There are various options for traveling and exploring the city's
              attractions. Singapore tours are often divided into different
              areas of interest.
            </p>
          </div>
          <div class="korea">
            <a
              href="https://www.nexttripholiday.com/korea/?gclid=Cj0KCQjw_O2lBhCFARIsAB0E8B-C7VZC07USIRlzFrUAUUGK_QBDvD-X9X5A59dkk2lwVwWsnrl8sg8aAtKtEALw_wcB"
              target="_blank"
            >
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1eb-9irarbPW3rSupUCpqqC_R0z5-oBlh/view?usp=sharing"
                alt="korea"
            /></a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Korea : Korea tours are an excellent choice for travelers seeking
              to experience impressive travel experiences in South Korea. This
              country offers a wide array of fascinating attractions, ranging
              from stunning natural landscapes to captivating cultural wonders,
              delicious cuisine, and bustling cities that should not be missed.
            </p>
          </div>
          <div class="canada">
            <a
              href="https://www.travelzeed.com/product?des=13&gclid=Cj0KCQjw_O2lBhCFARIsAB0E8B8dF8eeGgDezvEvC4_0GE8AEkwipHZkOScTPOR2FSz_GfyhaQqZrz0aAvLXEALw_wcB"
              target="_blank"
            >
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1RAv-Q_d98KWhdSNQe9cLHxvCWplM9Tx0/view?usp=drive_link"
                alt="canada"
            /></a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Canada : Canadian tours often provide travelers with unforgettable
              experiences both in cities and regions. You will have the
              opportunity to explore beautiful wildlife parks, visit stunning
              waterfalls, venture into snowy regions during winter, and learn
              about the culture of various ethnic groups and communities in the
              country.
            </p>
          </div>
          <div class="neterlands">
            <a
              href="https://www.mushroomtravel.com/tour/outbound/netherlands?md=ad&gclid=Cj0KCQjw_O2lBhCFARIsAB0E8B9g53lnBdhajqZIU38u_mUBNFrwXM4WERRb4I8rdeRE50__neV7ufQaAq1hEALw_wcB"
              target="_blank"
            >
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/1N5HBjbK5vc_0jZmrLmjslnZKmu2_u_2e/view?usp=drive_link"
                alt="neterlands"
            /></a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Neterlands :A tour of the Netherlands may allow you to experience
              the breathtaking nature and stunning landscapes, such as visiting
              snow-covered greenhouses in interesting amusement parks, exploring
              picturesque regions with beautiful natural scenery, and visiting
              beautiful seaside areas. Additionally, there are tours that focus
              on the culture and history of the Netherlands.
            </p>
          </div>
          <div class="paris">
            <a
              href="https://www.qualityexpress.co.th/tour/Europe?keyword=&country=Europe&Airport=All&page=1&view=list"
              target="_blank"
            >
              <img
                src="https://drive.google.com/file/d/12eDfazPZBAEBa6PUjtsV8oQm13MF64Fv/view?usp=sharing"
                alt="paris"
            /></a>
            <p style="font-size: 13px">
              Paris :Paris is interesting for tourists who want a romantic and
              culturally significant atmosphere. since the ancient culture
              Beautiful sights, delicious food and a hub for European art and
              culture. In addition, the main attractions in the city are
              explored. Including visiting and taking pictures at the Eiffel
              Tower.
            </p>
          </div>
        </div>
      </div>
    </div>
  </body>
</html>